<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Sources track raw/main so ReaPack always serves the current bridge instead
     of a pinned commit that silently drifts behind HEAD. @version here MUST move
     in lockstep with @version in bridge/reaper_agent_bridge.lua on every release,
     and these fixes must be merged to main before this is published. A tagged,
     pin-verified release pipeline is the proper next step (review Next-Level #3). -->
<index version="1" name="reaper-daemon" commit="main">
  <category name="bridge">
    <reapack name="reaper_agent_bridge.lua" type="script" desc="Reaper Daemon (REAPER agent file bridge)">
      <metadata>
        <link rel="website" href="https://github.com/wretcher207/reaper-daemon">Reaper Daemon on GitHub</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="3.8.1" author="Dead Pixel Design" time="2026-07-09T01:02:08Z">
        <changelog><![CDATA[Render-dialog-hang fix: a capture_track_audio or render no longer hangs the bridge on a fresh install. REAPER's render-progress window blocks the synchronous render until dismissed unless its "Automatically close when finished" checkbox is ticked; the bridge now forces that setting (renderclosewhendone bit 0) on for the render and restores the user's prior value afterward, via SWS. Without SWS it degrades gracefully and the reply carries render_autoclose_warning instead of risking the hang. Includes 3.8.0. Bridge robustness (Phase 4 of the 2026-07-02 review): a crash mid-render no longer bricks the bridge (render locks reclaim after 6h); command ids are sanitized before naming the outbox reply (path traversal + non-string crash closed); the singleton lock writes atomically; heartbeats now actually carry the in-flight-command marker so a long sampler load reads as busy, not dead; json decoder refuses null array elements (they silently shifted later elements) and lone low surrogates. Includes 3.6.0. Platform correctness (Phase 3 of the 2026-07-02 review): Windows error replies carry the real UPPER_SNAKE code (the drive letter in the script path used to decode every error as code "C"); Linux status/jam no longer report DEAD when pgrep misses the lowercase reaper binary (both names matched, and a miss defers to the heartbeat). Includes 3.5.0. Broken-features cluster (Phase 2 of the 2026-07-02 review): discover-map actually reads .midnam note names (GetTrackMIDINoteNameEx; the old call could never return a name); short drum lanes really loop (longer-than-section and non-dividing lanes tile correctly instead of rendering silence); riff accepts 24-bit PCM (REAPER's default record format) and WAVE_FORMAT_EXTENSIBLE; eq/setparam scan every FX parameter via paginated limit/offset (max_params was silently ignored, hiding EQ bands past index 200). Includes 3.4.0 (honesty cluster: requeue triage, stale-reply clear, evidence-gated eq/setparam/send exits).]]></changelog>
        <source main="main">https://github.com/wretcher207/reaper-daemon/raw/main/bridge/reaper_agent_bridge.lua</source>
        <source file="json.lua">https://github.com/wretcher207/reaper-daemon/raw/main/bridge/json.lua</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
</index>
